Farah Strike Pamphlets and Broadsides 5495
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Order Consolidating Cases, Consolidated Complaint, and Notice of Hearing, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Milo V. Price. February 1, 1974. Cases nos. 28-CC-462; 28-CC-472. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Decision and Order, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Edward B. Miller; John H. Fanning; John A. Penello. October 10, 1973. Case nos. 23-CP-78; 23- CP-83. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Settlement Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Louis V. Baldovin. June 27, 1973. Case no. 23-CB-1331. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Settlement Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Milo V. Price. January 30, 1974. Case nos. 28-CB-701; 28-CB-733; 28-CB-757. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Petition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Kenneth R. Carr. July 23, 1973. Case no. 23-RM-292. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Dear Mr. Frank Herrera, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Clifford W. Potter. June 15, 1972. Correspondence. Case no. 23-CA-4374. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Dear Mr. Donald D. Congress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Robert E. Allen. July 28, 1972. Correspondence. Case no. 23-CA-4374. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Dear Mr. Kenneth R. Carr, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Louis V. Baldovin. August 31, 1973. Correspondence. Case no. 23-RM-292. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Law Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Case nos. 28-CA-1997; 28-CA-1886. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Labor Law Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Case nos. 28-CA-2036; 28-CA-2054; 28-CA-2089; 28-CA-2099; 28-CA- 2109; 28-CA-2137; 28-CA-2152; 28-CA-2210. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor Law Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Case no. 28-CA-2735. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor Law Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Case no. 23-CA-4389. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor Law Reports, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Commerce Clearing House. Case no. 23-CA-4435. Item is in English.
- Notice to members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Notice to Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By G. Biggs. March 22, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Notice to Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By G. Biggs. March 22, 1973. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Notice to Employees and Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    February 27, 1974. Item is in English.
- Pamphlets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: For the Defence of Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Paul Newton Poling. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: For the Defence of Farah Workers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Paul Newton Poling. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Farah: The Union Struggle in the 70s, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Rex Hardesty. Reprinted from the The American Federationist. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Union Drive in the Southwest: Chicanos Strike at Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By San Francisco Bay Area Farah Stike Support Committee. January, 1974. Item is in English;Spanish.
  - Item 5: Victory for the Farah Strike: A Victory for Us All, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Farah Strike Support Committee. Item is in English;Spanish.
- United States Court of Appeals, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: ACWA v. NLRB; NLRB v. Farah, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By United States Court of Appeals, Fifth Circuit. March 21, 1974. Case nos. 73-2092; 73- 2600. Item is in English.